♪ You can't drop me,
you can't block me ♪
Who stop me? It's outside ♪
You should've known better ♪
♪ Or is it 'cause
I flow better? ♪
They kept me in the shade ♪
♪ But now I'm back,
motherfucker ♪
♪ It's the nigga
with the cannon for the two ♪
Swingin' with the braids ♪
♪ Don't fuck,
don't fuck with the braids ♪
♪ They can't fuck, they can't
fuck with the braids ♪
♪ Don't fuck,
don't fuck with the braids ♪
♪ They can't fuck, they can't
fuck with the braids ♪
Woof, woof, woof, braids ♪
Woof, woof, woof, braids... ♪
Got-dang! Whoo!
♪ At night I can't sleep,
I toss and turn ♪
Candlesticks in the dark ♪
♪ Visions of bodies
bein' burned ♪
♪ Four walls just
starin' at a nigga ♪
♪ I'm paranoid, sleepin' with
my finger on the trigger... ♪
Yeah, all right.
Okay.
My favorite.
That's real nice.
You find everything okay today,
big fella?
Actually, man, no.
Uh, do y'all sell, uh,
cast-iron skillets here?
Well, if you don't see any
on the shelf,
then we don't have 'em in stock.
But I'll check, just to be sure.
All right.
Uh, do y'all sell, uh,
animal repellant here?
Did you see it on the shelf?
Nope.
No, we don't have any s...
Nope, we don't have
any skillets in stock,
but, um,
I can order one in for you.
Be here in a couple weeks.
No, man, that's...
It's all good, man.
I'll just get it somewhere else.
I appreciate it, though.
You're just gonna order it
on Amazon, aren't you?
No, man. No.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Hey, guys. It's your boy,
"These Backhoes Ain't Loyal."
Thanks for coming out
to my channel today.
If you want to see more
backhoe tractor content,
make sure you hit that
"subscribe" button.
Ah, shit.
You can even give this video
a thumbs-up.
So, what we're gonna do today
is we're gonna get
down and dirty...
...and we're gonna change
the oil in this tractor.
But before I get
under this hoe...
- ...we're gonna make sure that
all the wheels are secure.
- God...
But I've done told you,
these backhoes ain't loyal.
They'll roll over you
in a second.
I'm serious, dudes.
I lost two uncles this way.
Oh, shit, shit, shit!
Shit.
Oh, shit!
♪ She don't like
my white bitch ♪
Say I act too light-skinned ♪
♪ Dolla, don't be trifling,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm dirty in the streets,
In bed she a freak ♪
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Kiss my feet,
take this meat... ♪
Hello?
Hey!
Whatever's in there,
you better squawk or chirp
or sing a fucking song
with your little furry friends
or something.
Boo, motherfuck...
Oh, goddamn, man.
Get...
Oh, goddamn!
Shit!
Hmm.
Oh, God.
Go.
- Go back just one.
- Go back one?
Yeah.
Oh, boy, this is bad.
You got feral hogs.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
So, what I need,
hog repellant or something?
No, not as simple as that.
Here, give me that.
Let's see.
Yeah. Shit, you can thank
the explorer Hernando de Soto
for this bullshit.
Were the turds wet or dry?
I do not know.
Well, did they crumble
in your hand?
Can you just tell me
how to get rid
of these damn things,
please, man?
I don't want to stand here
all day
talking to you
about dookie and shit.
All right, well, uh, clearly,
they're coming after
whatever it is you're growing.
Now, I-I can't make it out
from that photo,
so what kind of crops are these?
Corn.
- Oh. (sighs) Yeah.
- Yeah, man, lots of...
lots of corn.
Oh, they love that stuff.
They love that stuff.
Um... okay.
Here's what I'd do
if I were you.
You take a bunch
of that corn, right?
Set it out in an open area.
Now, soon as that dirty hog
shows up
and starts chowing down on it,
you line up your shot,
take it out.
- Okay.
- All right.
Now, if he starts to run,
you aim for the nose
and you don't stop firing
till that fucker goes down.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, then you move in close.
- Head shot.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Uh, can I just poison it
or something, man?
I don't think you understand.
This is serious.
Now, these things,
they ain't no bedtime story
animals, you know?
I mean, they don't deserve
no sympathy.
They are aggressive,
they are invasive,
and they will not stop
until they destroy
everything you have.
You got to kill them
before they kill you.
What?
Before they kill me? Okay.
The hogs?
A pack of hogs killed a woman
in Texas about a year ago.
Just outside of Houston.
Chewed her ass up.
Okay.
All right, but this isn't funny.
No, man, yeah, it is, man.
Bedtime story animal.
All right, guys, now that we gt
all that old, dirty oil
out of there,
I'm gonna show you
what some fresh, new,
healthy oil looks like here.
And this is where it goes.
Now, check back next week,
and I'm gonna show you
how to replace a carburetor.
Thank you, guys,
for stopping by.
Make sure you hit
that "subscribe" button.
Okay, baby.
Let's do this, mama.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on, baby, come on.
Oh, shit.
All right, let's see.
All right.
Oh, fuck!
Come on, man. Come on, man.
God!
All right, man. All right.
All right.
All right, man, all right.
All right, man, come on.
How big is this motherfuck...
Fuck!
Okay.
All right, baby.
Yep.
Yeah.
♪ Because-a in-a me eyes
there is red like blood ♪
♪ And I been moving around
like a human flood ♪
♪ Smoke outta me mouth
and outta me nose... ♪
I'm gonna avenge you.
I promise.
Gonna roast this motherfucker.
Dinner's served, motherfucker.
Come and get it.
♪ Under me sleng teng,
me under me ♪
♪ Because it's way in my brain,
no cocaine ♪
♪ I don't wanna,
I don't wanna go insane ♪
Way in my brain, no cocaine ♪
♪ I don't wanna,
I don't wanna go insane ♪
Oh, no ♪
It's way in my brain ♪
♪ I said me smoke it and me
pass it through the window ♪
♪ And me give it to
my next-door neighbor... ♪
If the chicks don't feed
within 36 hours, they'll starv.
Incredibly, it survives.
But it's stunned.
Oh, shit!
Oh, come on, mama. Let's do it.
Whoo!
Yeah, baby!
Yeah, mother...
That's what I'm talking about!
All right. All right, all right,
all right, all right, okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay. Okay. Push down.
Okay. All right, o-okay.
Come on, baby. Oh...
Yeah, man.
Whoo!
Oh, we outside!
Shoo-bob, shoo-bob, doo-ooh ♪
Are you rolling ♪
♪ Down the same street
that I'm going ♪
♪ Up the same stream
that I'm folding ♪
Oh!
On the new ride? ♪
Shoo-bob, shoo-bob, doo-ooh ♪
High is high ♪
Low is low ♪
Everybody wanna go to heaven ♪
But nobody wants to die ♪
Nobody wants to ♪
Are you rolling ♪
♪ Down the same street
that I'm going ♪
♪ Up the same stream
that I'm folding... ♪
Oh, shit!
Oh, shit.
All right.
Shit.
Goddamn.
Oh, shit!
Oh, sh...
Ah, shit!
Oh, fu...
Oh, shit!
Fu...
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Oh, shit.
God.
Oh, thank God.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Oh, come on, bitch,
I know you see me.
Hey, hey, hey!
Shit!
Help me!
♪ If you got
the strength I do ♪
Then sign me up ♪
If I'm not too much for you ♪
Help!
- Sign me up ♪
-♪ I'm a little bit
unraveled... ♪
- Hey!
Hey!
Hey, fuck! Help!
Hey, help me!
Hey, shit! Help!
Help. Help me, plea...
Help.
Fucking help.
Oh, bitch, fucking please.
Oh, shit!
Fuck! What the fuck?
Fuck off!
Get the fuck off me!
Fucking...
Shit!
Motherfucker, die!
Let go!
Fucking die!
Get the fuck off me.
Yo.
Hey, hey.
What's up, man?
Chillin', man. Chillin'.
Yeah, I hope so. I hope so.
- What's up? You need something?
- It's in my email, okay?
Yeah, um, the lawyer sent over
that contract. It looks okay.
I still have some questions
about the dates, though.
Oh.
We'll get it sorted.
Don't worry.
How is it out there?
Is it boring?
Yeah. Yeah.
You-you sound tired, man.
Nah, man. Nah, man.
I'm straight. I'm good.
I'm straight.
Just send it to me.
Send it to my email,
and my assistant
will worry about it, okay?
Thank you so much.
Hey, look, can I call you back
tomorrow, bruh?
Uh, yeah, yeah. You good?
Mm-hmm.
All right, man.
I-I'll talk to you tomorrow.
- All right. Peace.
- Peace.
Yo.
What's up?
What's up, man?
Are you eating bacon
and drinking whiskey?
Hibiki, bro.
Cheers, nigga.
Breakfast of champion.
Yo, man, it's the farm life.
Yeah, what was going on
yesterday?
What were you doing?
What happened to your face?
I don't know, man, it's just...
Hey, I was out there
with that tractor.
I got that up and running, right?
And, um, just did some shooting.
You know.
This-this ain't nothing.
Look, man, I know this is
your safe farm and all that,
but you got to be careful
out there, okay?
Farms are dangerous as fuck.
Okay, and you're over there
by yourself, too, man.
If something happens to you,
you fall on a rake headfirst,
no one's gonna know it
for like weeks.
Message received, bruh.
You know, the whole point of
this farm is to have options.
If you don't like it, you don't
have to keep it, you know.
You can go back to the city.
At-Atlanta's not going anywher,
you know.
It's all good, man.
It's pretty much
slow motion around here.
Yeah.
Ain't got to worry about me.
Only thing I need to worry about
is this damn neck, man.
Every time I move it,
it feels like
I'm on pins and needles
and shit.
Were you outside
for a long time yesterday?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think y-you're sunburn.
No, no.
Yes.
You ever been sunburned before?
Nigga, look at me.
Do I look like...
Hell no, I ain't been sunburned.
Black people
can't get sunburned.
What you talking about?
Yes, yes, they can.
White people can get ashy.
Black people can get sunburned.
It's-it's a fact.
So, you telling me Wesley Snipes
can get sunburned?
Yes, Wesley Snipes
can get sunburned.
Okay, all right,
what about... what's...
uh, what's-his-name...
uh, "Kiss from a Rose"?
He can get sunburned, too?
Yes. Yes, Seal can get...
Dark niggas
can get sunburned, bruh.
I don't know, man.
All right, hold up.
What about Captain Phillips?
Come on.
- I'm gonna assume you mean
the Somalian pirate...
- Yeah.
- ...not Tom Hanks.
- Yeah. Yeah.
And it doesn't matter, 'cause
they can both get sunburned.
Nigga, I would... Who-who's
going to be a pirate on the sea
under the sun the whole day
if they can get sunburned?
I know this shit ain't true,
man. It's just not true.
♪ Don't let the sun
catch you crying ♪
Crying at my front door ♪
You done daddy dirty ♪
♪ He sure don't
want you no more ♪
♪ Don't let the sun
catch you lying ♪
Lying at my front door ♪
Daddy's done turned salty ♪
♪ And, baby,
you made him so sore ♪
You can cry, cry, cry ♪
Yes, baby, you can wail ♪
♪ Beat your head
on the pavement ♪
♪ Till the man comes
and throws you in. ♪
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH